{
    "id": "0227824cd63145919c36d05e375d41ab",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………….. surprisingly, we missed the train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Not",
                "No"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I can see you tomorrow, but …………………. on Tuesday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "not",
                "no"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Let me know if you have ………………… trouble.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "some"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. people have ever seen her laugh.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Few",
                "Less"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Is she here …………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "yet",
                "already",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He denied that he had …………………. seen her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ever",
                "never"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. you say, I won’t believe you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "No matter what",
                "Whatever"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. support the conservative party.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "no more",
                "no longer"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. are going to be rainy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "The next days",
                "The next few days"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. was there.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Neither of my parents",
                "None of my parents"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}